

ERKUT KAYA

Candidate Web Developer

erkut.kaya@outlook.com

linkedin.com/erkut-kaya

Creative Skills

Teamwork

Googling

Problem Solving

Software Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

ReactJS

SQL C++

C#

Tools

Visual Studio

Visual Studio Code

MS Office

Microsoft SQL Server

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

Profile

I am a 4th year student of Computer Engineering department at Eskisehir Osmangazi University. I want to follow the technological developments in the field of technology and digitalization, make improvements in the system, improve customer satisfaction and loyalty, and improve the user experience.

Education

2017-Present Eskisehir Osmangazi University (Eskisehir)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

2012-2016 Ertugrul Kurdoglu High School (Kocaeli)

2004-2012 Ibni Sina Primary School (İstanbul)

Experience

09/2021 - 10/2021 Intern / Anadolu University, Eskisehir

- Focused on website design and software development using Html, Css, JavaScript, Excel and Adobe Photoshop.

07/2021 - 08/2021 Intern / Anadolubank, Istanbul

- Built a representative web application of banking using Html, Css, JavaScript, Bootstrap and ReactJS.

Certificates

Udemy

Front End Web Development Bootcamp (October 2021)

BTK Akademi

Project Management (October 2021)

BTK Akademi

Introduction to Social Media Specialist (October 2021)

Google

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (September 2021)

BTK Akademi

Availability of Websites (September 2021)

Cisco

Networking Essentials (Jun 2021)

Hobbies

- ChessWalking
- Music
- Video Games
- Cycling
- Drawing

Preferences

Dr. Şahin IŞIK

Assistant Proffessor, Eskisehir Osmangazi University

Email: sahini@ogu.edu.tr